翻译: 宛若安宁  Amber  B'S
前情介紹
Previously on Mike & Molly:
Molly現在是作家了
Molly is a writer now.
噢
Oh.
校对: 店小二
你怎么沒早說 讓我在書架上給你空出地方來
Why didn't you say so? Let me clear a spot in my bookcase.
后期: Danica
這是常有的事啊
You know, it just so happens
有很多普通女性 就像我一樣
that there are a lot of regular women, just like me,
压制: 凯撒
寫出了賣座的作品
who have written best-selling books.
我受夠了 我們打一架吧
That's it, we're doing this.
動手吧 來啊
Make your move, come on.
吃我一拳
I'll give you one swing...
不 不 行了 別打了
No, no, come on, nobody's fighting!
嗨
Hey.
寫什么呢
What you writing?
就試寫個短篇小說
Oh, just experimenting with a short story.
真的  我喜歡短篇小說 因為
Really? I like short stories 'cause,
它們很短
you know, they're short.
能看看嗎
Can I take a look?
哦 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
還沒打算公開于世呢
It's not ready for public consumption.
哦 別這樣
Oh, come on.
我都把給芝加哥熊隊寫的詩給你看了
I showed you that poem I wrote about the Chicago Bears.
是啊 我記得
Yeah, I remember, uh...
"跟隨Ditka教練的指揮棒
"The Hall of Fame will admitcha,
美國前王牌橄欖球教練 曾執教于芝加哥熊隊
你終將登上名人堂"
if you listen to Coach Ditka."
我很好奇他聽過沒有
I wonder if he ever got it.
那你至少告訴我故事梗概吧
So, can you at least tell me what the story's about?
呃 我想想
Uh, let's see.
是關于一個男人和一個女人
It's about a man and a woman and...
以及他們的日常生活
the day-to-day stuff they go through.
- 就這樣  - 嗯
- That's it? - Mm-hmm.
那個 至少有點色情的吧
Well, is it at least sexy?
色情 才怪 噗
Sexy? No. Pfft!
好吧 等你寫好了 我非常愿意讀
Okay. Well, when you're ready, I would love to read it.
沒問題
You got it.
-好的 愛你  - 我也愛你
- Okay. Love you.  - Love you, too.
對了
By the way,
我知道肯定有色情的
I know it's sexy.
噗 你在說什么呀
Pfft! What are you talking about?
我都認識你這么久了
Because in all the time I have known you,
你從來都不說"噗"
you have never once gone "Pfft!"
什么 噗 我剛剛就說了啊
What? Pfft! I just did it.
我一直都說
I do it all the time.
太可笑了 噗
Ridiculous. Pfft!
哦
Oh.
嗨 Victoria
Hey, Victoria.
是啊 酒吧還有優惠時段
Yeah, we're still on for happy hour.
我不知道 來杯伏特加湯力
I don't know, a vodka tonic?
現在才早上8點
8:00 in the morning.
我一定要馬上決定嗎
Do I really have to decide now?
好吧 聽著 我在工作 掛啦
Okay, listen, I'm working. I gotta go.
再見
Bye. Bye.
Bye.
好啦 開始寫派對吧
Okay. Let's get this party started.
喔 你在耍老娘吧
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
好了  知道了 知道了
All right, I get it. I get it.
我聽見啦
We hear you.
行了 我聽見啦
All right, we hear you.
你想當個皮納塔是吧
You want to be a piata?
一種玩具 在動物玩偶中裝上糖果 掛在天花板上供兒童敲打
最慘的
Worst...
皮納塔
...piata...
沒有之一
... ever.
哈
Ha!
耶 哼
Yeah. Huh?
閉上你的臭嘴 閉嘴 閉嘴
Shut you up, shut up, shut up.
別動了你
Stop moving.
別動
Stop moving!
哦 你
Yeah, you...
希望已經見血了
I wish there was blood.
哦 你個兔崽子
Oh, you son of a bitch.
你到底在哪兒呢
Where are you?!
到底是哪個 哼
Which one of you is it, huh?
問問廚房里的小伙伴下場如何
Now ask your friend in the kitchen how this is gonna end!
看你干的好事
See what you did?!
迈克和茉莉
第四季 第三集
电波诚译
好啦
There you go.
再也沒有尷尬的斑禿了
No more embarrassing bald spot.
Victoria
Victoria.
哦 我還沒干完 進來吧
Yeah, I'm not done yet. Come on in.
想都別想
Not a chance.
沒什么可怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
不敢茍同
Beg to differ.
哦 別孩子氣了 快進來吧
Oh, don't be a baby. Get in here.
好吧
Fine.
我進來了
I'm in.
你看天花板干什么啊
Why are you looking up at the ceiling?
因為那兒沒尸體啊
Because there are no dead people up there.
那你得抬頭看上好一會兒了
Well, you're gonna be looking up there for a while
因為我還需要大概一小時
'cause I need like another hour.
開什么玩笑 哦 老天爺啊
Are you kidding? Oh, God!
你怎么不給我打電話
Why didn't you call me?
對不起
Sorry.
我忙著給一個毒販子的
I got caught up trying to plug the holes
腦袋填窟窿呢
in that drug dealer's head.
我該直接給他帶個帽子
I might just put a hat on him.
或者來個頭巾
Maybe a do-rag.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
捂上眼睛 有必要嗎
Covering your eyes? Really?
有 我不想把死人的樣子
Yes, I prefer not to have the images of death
印在我腦子里
seared into my brain.
你想不想看個大腦
Do you want to see a brain?
不 不
No. No!
你確定 我這兒罐子里正好有一個
Are you sure? 'Cause I got one here right in a jar.
不 不 我去車里等你 哦
No, no, I'll wait for you in the car. Oh!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
抱歉
Sorry.
哦
Oh!
嗨
Hello?
有人在家嗎
Anybody home?
Molly
Molly?
哦 "Mike
Oh. "Mike,
和Victoria出去喝一杯
Having a drink with Victoria.
晚點兒見 M"
See you later. M."
看來家里只有我嘍
Well, I guess it's just me.
只有我 是吧
It is just me, right?!
哦 不能這樣 大錯特錯啊
Oh, this is wrong. This is so wrong.
我是狡詐的大傻貓[卡通人物]
I am a bad puddy tat.
哼
Huh.
好的 加密保護 聰明啊
Okay, password protected. Smart.
"麥克和茉莉"
"Mike and Molly."
這就進來了
And I'm in.
"M的故事"
"The Story of M."
"他如火般的熱情 喚醒了她內心
"The warmth of his excitement awoke something inside her.
動物的野性"
Something animal."
"噗" 沒有的事
"Pfft," My ass.
"她饑渴的向后伸出手臂
"She reached back with her eager hand
貪婪的索求著他腫脹的分身"
and greedily sought his turgid girth."
分身 我倒是懂 至于腫脹嘛 我就不太肯定了
Girth, I know. Turgid, I'm not so sure about.
不行 不能再看了
No, that's enough, that's enough.
哎 我在騙誰呢
Oh, who am I kidding?
我現在就需要喝一杯了
I could really use that drink about now.
馬上好了
Almost done.
三具尸體前 你就這么說
You said that three bodies ago.
進來吧 我可以和你作伴
Come on in. You can keep me company.
我不敢 抱歉
I can't. Sorry.
你當然可以
Sure you can.
你只需要一步一步來
You just got to do this one step at a time.
來 看看Kilgallon夫人
Here. Look at Mrs. Kilgallon.
我 不想看
I... don't want to.
看看嘛
Just look at her.
她是個好人 在睡夢中平靜地死去
She was a nice old lady who died peacefully in her sleep.
身上沒有彈孔嗎
So, no bullet holes?
就有個低腰紋身而已
Well, just a tramp stamp, believe it or not.
這種紋身通常是放蕩女的標志
好吧 我看
All right, I'll look.
哎喲 天哪
Ooh-hoo, ooh.
看 我在看她呢
Look, I'm looking.
沒什么好怕的吧
See? Nothing to be scared of.
是的 你說得對
Nope. You're right.
你想摸一下嗎
Do you want to touch her?
不 我做不到 噢噢噢
No, I couldn't, no. Ooh-hoo-hoo.
她不介意的
She doesn't mind.
我介意 我介意
I mind, I mind.
你干嘛一直傻笑
Why are you giggling?
不知道 我停不下來
I don't know. But I can't stop.
就輕輕戳一下她
Just give her a little poke.
戳她 不行 我不能戳她
Poke? No, no poking, can't poke.
這對你寫作有好處啊
This will be great for your writing.
你總是說想要些不一樣的經歷
You're always saying that you want to experience new things
然后寫到書里去
so that you can describe them.
我確實說過 是嗎
Ugh, I did say that, didn't I?
好
Okay.
噢 呼呼呼
Ooh. Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo.
噢 吼
Ooh! Ooh!
我做到了 我摸了她
I did it. I touched her.
我摸了一個死人 哇哦
I touched a dead lady. Ooh.
看吧 沒什么大不了的
See? It's no big deal.
其實 她比我想象中冷很多誒
Actually, she's a lot colder than I thought she'd be.
就像
It's like...
就像 在摸一根臘腸
it's like, uh, touching bologna.
說起這個 冰箱里有些熟食 你餓嗎
That reminds me, I got some cold cuts in the fridge. You hungry?
我的天哪 她睜眼睛了
Ooh. Oh, God, she opened her eyes.
快看啊 她睜眼睛了
Look-it, she opened her eyes!
冷靜點
Calm down.
有時會這樣的啦
Sometimes this happens.
噢 啊
Oh. Aah!
碰到臘腸了 啊
Bologna. Aah!
"他很無助
"He was helpless,
他的雙手被綁在背后
His hands bound behind his back
而她用饑渴的小嘴貪婪地含住他的"
while her hungry mouth greedily enveloped his sw..."
- 嘿 大個子  - 啊 沒什么
- Yo, big guy. - Oh, nothing!
你在干嘛
What you doing?
就是吃點東西
Just grabbing a bite.
Molly不在家 誰也沒在家
Molly's not home, nobody's home,
我什么也沒做
I didn't do anything.
那是Molly的電腦嗎
That Molly's laptop?
是吧 我想是的
Yeah, I be... I believe that is.
她很注重電腦里的個人隱私
She's pretty private about what's on there.
你沒偷看 對吧
You're not reading it, are you?
沒有 噗
No. Pfft.
好吧
All right.
明早見
See you in the morning.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Night. - Night.
- Mike  - 沒什么
- Mike. - Nothing!
天哪
Oh, boy.
我的天哪
Oh, God.
你還好吧
You okay?
我十分想要消毒液
Well, I'd kill for some Purell.
抱歉 Kilgallon夫人沖你翻白眼
Sorry Mrs. Kilgallon gave you the hairy eyeball.
真不知道你怎么能以此為生的
I don't know how you can do this for a living.
這很平常啊
Oh, it's like anything.
習慣就好了
You get used to it.
是啊 可是你不會覺得有點悲催嗎
Yeah, but doesn't it make you a little sad?
有時候 當然會
Sometimes, sure.
不過這么多年了 也有一些應付的法子
But over the years, you find little ways to cope.
- 比如什么  - 比如大麻
- Like what? - Like marijuana.
來點嗎
Want some?
不 這不是我的菜
No, that's not my thing.
你確定
You sure?
小小一口煙 飄飄入仙山
Just a little toke to take the edge off.
- 不  - 我們本來要去喝酒
- No. We were gonna go drinking.
這只是殊途同歸的
This is just a different approach
解決問題的辦法
to solving the same problem.
什么問題
What problem?
生活啊 親愛的
Life, baby.
好吧
Okay, fine.
點吧
Fire it up.
我得告訴你
All right, I should tell you,
我上次抽大麻 還是上大學時
the last time I smoked pot was in college and it didn't
而且對我沒什么用
have much effect on me.
誰是死人
Who's a dead person?
你是死人
You're a dead person.
是你 是你 就是你
Oh, yes, you are. Oh, yes, you are.
"他一把抓住她栗色的頭發
"He grabbed a fistful of her chestnut hair
"將她脫至窗前
"And dragged her to the bay window
"整座城市
"Where the entire town
"都能看到她的屈服
"Could see her surrender.
"她別無選擇
"She had no choice.
面對他高漲的巨物 她甘做奴隸"
She was a slave to his tumescent length."
我的媽呀
Yikes.
誰能想到你那溫柔可人的妻子
Who'd have thought your meek little wife
居然知道勃起的50種不同說法
knew 50 different words for boner?
她上過大學的
She went to college.
你懂的 詞匯量自然會增大
You know, your vocabulary expands.
"增大" 真有意思
"Expands." That's funny.
太狂野了
It's wild.
她的日記從沒這么黃啊
Her-her diary's nowhere near this dirty.
你看過她的日記嗎
You read her diary?
你還黑了她電腦呢
You hacked her computer.
我們的手都不干凈
We all have blood on our hands.
好吧 算了
All right, all right.
關鍵是 我現在該怎么做
The question is, what do I do now?
告訴你 我會怎么做
I know what I'd do.
我會把這個當猶太法典一樣研習
I'd study this thing like it was the Talmud.
什么
What?
你老婆給了你通往她秘密濕地
Your wife just handed you an erogenous road map
的情欲地圖啊
to her protected wetlands.
好好使用
Use it.
才不要呢
No.
我又不是那種"癡迷捆綁
I'm not really the "Kinky, tie 'em up,
喜歡在人家私處亂插東西"的人
put things where they don't belong" Kind of guy.
這么做又不是為了你
Well, this isn't about you.
是因為Molly想嘗試新事物
It's about Molly wanting to try new things.
如果一個人每天早上
I mean, how would you like it if someone
都給你做一堆同樣的煎餅 你會怎么想
served you the same stack of pancakes every morning?
你在開玩笑嗎
Are you kidding?
這可是他日思夜想的美事
That's his fantasy.
這么說會讓他的胃口"腫"起來的
You just made his stomach turgid.
我的意思是
What I'm saying is,
你應該走出自己的安樂模式
you might have to step outside your comfort zone
去取悅你老婆
to please your wife.
啊
Aw.
這就是為啥我和Joyce能夠和睦相處
That's why Joyce and I are so compatible.
讓我穿什么 吃什么 做什么都成
I will wear, eat or do anything.
什么都成哦
Anything.
啊
Aah!
腮紅這一塊你得小心處理
You got to go easy on the blush.
家屬不希望老人家看起來像個妓女
Relatives hate it when grandma looks like a whore.
知道嗎 我上次出席葬禮
You know, the last time
還是爸爸去世時
I was at a funeral was Dad's.
那有一陣子了吧
That was a while back.
是的 我當時八歲
Yeah, I was... eight.
那時我一直希望他突然
I kept, I kept hoping that he was gonna
坐起來 然后大喊"驚喜哦"
sit up and yell, "Surprise."
他沒有這么做
And he didn't.
是的 他沒這么做
No, he... he didn't.
我都不記得這事了
I don't remember any of that.
唉 妹子 那時你才三歲
Well, sweetie, you were three.
你一點都不記得了嗎
You remember him at all?
不記得了
Not really.
只記得啤酒 須后水還有香煙的味道
Just the smell of beer and Hai Karate and smoke.
但也有可能是媽媽的
But that could've been Mom.
你會喜歡他的
You would have liked him.
他很有趣  而且脾氣很好
He was really funny and... and sweet-tempered.
他就像 一只巨型的泰迪熊
He was like a... he was like a giant teddy bear.
聽著像Mike
Sounds like Mike.
哈
Huh.
還真是的
How about that.
告訴你個好消息 這些死人生意
Well, the good news is I'm clearly not freaked-out
再也嚇不到我了
by any of this dead business anymore.
不錯
Good.
我覺得你現在可以接受這個了
Then I think you're ready for this.
你這輩子看過這么大的蛋蛋嗎
You ever seen balls this big in your life?
我要再去嗨上幾口
I'm gonna need more pot.
嗯 啊
Mmm. Aw.
兄弟們
Gentlemen.
嘿 還以為你今晚不出來了呢
Hey, I thought you were staying in tonight.
是啊 Molly和她妹妹出去了
Yeah, well, Molly's out with her sister
所以我決定還是出來和你們混
so I thought maybe I'd join you boys.
給我哥們 每人再來一瓶
Can I get a round for my friends?
咋啦
What?
你還好吧
Everything okay?
很好啊 怎么了
Yeah, it's all good. Why?
你 叫我們哥們 而且還請客
Y-You called us friends, and you're buying.
有意思
Very funny.
鷹隊換了新的進攻戰術 對吧
I see the Eagles are running that new offense, huh?
不明白為什么總有人喜歡
I don't know why you would
改變本來管用的東西呢
go and change something that's working.
這是明智之舉
Well, there is wisdom
把不同的戰術糅合起來
in mixing things up so the defense
讓對手防不勝防
can't predict your every move.
扯淡吧
That's crap.
橫沖直撞 頭破血流式的橄欖球
Straight-ahead, smash-mouth football.
也許不優雅
May not be pretty,
但能確保每次都完成任務
but it gets the job done every time.
不 我同意Samuel
No, I agree with Samuel.
不墨守成規才能讓比賽充滿刺激
Changing the playbook puts excitement back into the game.
比賽本身就夠刺激了
There's plenty of excitement in the game.
基礎才是最重要的 可惡
It's all about fundamentals, damn it.
哇哦
Whoa.
好吧
Okay.
是房事不順心吧
So, problems in the bedroom?
你自個兒買單吧
Buy your own stupid drinks.
喔
Ooh.
靈柩
Caskets.
那邊那個
That one there?
貌似五萬美元呢
Like $50,000.
比我的車還貴
That's more than my car.
值得擁有
Worth it.
上車
Hop in.
試駕一下吧
Give it a test drive.
不要
No way.
來嘛 我常這么干的
Come on, I do it all the time.
什么 別
What? No.
這可是打盹的最佳地點
It's a perfect place to take a nap.
那是因為你瘋了
'Cause you're crazy.
晚上好 Flynn女士 一起來吧
Good evening, Ms. Flynn. Won't you join me?
我也想試試
I want to try that.
哦
Oh,
我要進棺材咯
I'm getting in a coffin.
我要進棺材咯 喔喔喔
I'm getting in a coffin. Ooh-hoo-hoo, ooh.
我在棺材里
I'm in a coffin.
真是舒服死了
This is extremely comfortable.
對吧
Right?
躺下 躺下 躺下
Get down, get down, get d...
住手
Stop it.
噢
Ouch.
要來點妙脆角嗎
Do you want a Bugle?
別誤會 但殯儀館實在爽爆了
I'm sorry, but funeral parlors rock.
我感覺對不起那個清潔工
I just feel bad for the cleaning lady.
咱們怎么知道她媽剛去世啊
How were we supposed to know she'd just lost her mother?
晚安
Good night.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
我丈夫可是個警察
I'm married to a cop.
我身上有大麻味兒嗎
Do I smell like mara-hoochie?
沒有 只有尸體和玉米粒的味道
No. Just cadavers and Corn Nuts.
太好了
Great.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night.  - Good night.
晚安 Vince
Good night, Vince.
怎么了
What?
晚安 媽
Good night, Mom.
噢 大麻味兒
Ooh, the pot.
Mike
Mike?
噢 嘿 Mol
Oh, hey, Mol.
你在干啥
What you doing?
你非得問的話 我沒忍住 偷看了
If you have to ask, I failed.
我得更改登錄密碼了 是嗎
Do I have to change the password on my laptop?
這個想法不錯
Probably a good idea.
幫我打開手銬吧
Can you take these cuffs off?
可以啊 等我爽完再說
Yeah. When I'm done with you.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组